Hey everyone 1 second welcome you and you take
myself Gaurav and through this particular
video of today we are going to understand that how can
you draw circle and lips on any image.
Whenever we need to hide someone's face
then what do we do, we
use circle. Many times you must have
seen such images where if you want to hide
anyone's face then a
circle is made there and it is
blurred or it is
filled with a complete color here or if
I talk about lips in this way then a lip is
made and you reduce everything here on these lips. So
watch today's video, you will understand that
how can we draw these two things here
through OpenCC model. Now for this I
need an image. So we have a
lot of images here, we can use any of these images. So
right now I am
going to take this image of Disha Patani
and make it completely circle.  It is
above this and I am going to create it above this
so I am going to do both the commands here so let's go
here inside the pad file and do this so
now I am inside the pad file
so first of all my command will be
present here and after that
what will we do after the image, after that we will
also create a circle and then you are going to create it
so I am going to import it here
how to do it and let's run
it next thing now to create a circle here
first of all I need an image so
I am creating an oldest core here
a variable by the name of imc now this has been
created by the name of old image first I will get the
old file and we will create a circle on it then
a new file will be created so
what will we do with the new file, we will open it and
show it to you so that's why I have created it by the name of old image
and after that I have created cv2
dot here I am with you the read function
here I will use it to
read out the file now this I am read
function has been done inside this I am read I will have to bring the
image that shows the direction
its name is  Img four dot
jpg so I am taking Img four
jpg here here this is my
image here now I have to see the image whether the
image is big or small so
right now this image looks very big so I have to
make it a little smaller, I have to
resize it so that
it can fit comfortably inside my frame that means
inside the frame of my laptop
here I am going to do cc two
dot here I will do recise so that our image will be recised and what
research do I have to do so
I said I have to recise the old image
and for how much do I have to do it so I
said I have to recise it within ₹500 * 6
let's see this old image once so to
see the old image I am going to do
cc two dot here I will
use the show function here so that I can
base the image on it I will have to create a frame
and I am naming the frame after that
next now what do I have to do
here this name is added after the name comes now
I have to create a frame  You will have to show
which image to show, so I want to show the old image,
next, to
close this frame, I will have to press cc tu dot
here, wait, I can put
this image here, I
can close it and after this, I want to destroy the image that
you have here, the window, so by using
destroy all windows,
what will I do, I will destroy the windows
and I will run it, so see,
my image here is today's and a very
good image, it looks quite clean here,
now I
will mark a circle on it, there will be a lift here, so to
make a circle, here first of all
you need a variable inside which
my new image will be created with the circle,
now what do you have, see, first your
image comes, after that an image of a circle
comes, here as we call canvas,
what you have on it gets pasted
and a new image
comes out from there, so what will you have on top of the old image, it will be
pasted,
after pasting a new image will be created, so I will press new here  I will
create it once with the name of underscore img which will create a new image and
what will it do cv2 yes your cv2 here is
cc you dot here there is a function named circle here
yes what am I doing here I
will use the function named circle to
create a circle and I will
put a new image here now after putting it in new here
I can see my new image
now there are many parameters inside the function named circle in which
you have image color ready sickness line
tiles etc. there are many things so let's
see what these things are
and how they are reduced so I will
keep them here first of all if we
talk about the image then first of all you will see your
old image on which you have to
make a circle so I will
do that here with the old image on which you have to
make a circle the second thing is your center and radius
after that you will get the color its thickness will come
online then you have all these things so
first of all I will give us the color
here what is the center and what is the radius
so I will go back  Let me take the old image
in which I will talk about the circle and radius,
about the center and radius,
so see, this is your circle to be made, to
make this circle, first of all, you will
need a center for the image on which you want to make the circle, what
happened here, the center is done, so I will
write here that this is the center, now
how much radius should it be from this center,
means what should be the radius, like
I wrote it should be of 18 radius here,
so this circle is going to be
made inside you in a perfect uniform,
let's see it here, how it is going to be
made, so if I
talk about the center inside the circle here, then see
where do I have to place the center, so according to that image,
I will have to decide
where to place the center, so let's do one thing, first I have
500 600 images and
inside the image also your image is quite high,
I will open it once and show you,
this is your image on the right inside this image,
I have to place it here, approximately from here to
below and from here to this side, I will have to
make a circle of point somewhere here, then  This circle will be able to
cover up, I will have to take the center of the circle,
so I will keep almost anything inside it,
like I have
kept the center here, 200, 200, once
and if we talk about radius, then
how much radius can be kept with you, so I will
keep it in radius, I will
keep radius around 100 and after that
how do I want to show the color, so
I want to show green color, so anyway there are
busy R colors, here you have
B zero and B zero inside busy R, if you want
G, then I put 255 inside G, I
need perfect color for this
and you have R color, I need zero, right, if we
talk about it, then I need this much thickness, that
means you have the thickness of the line here,
how much do you want, so I need the thickness of the line
here around four, if we talk about nine type, then
inside the line type you have
different line types, like
here you will see, there are different, I am doing 16 things inside it,
so here I have done  I have
done thing 16, see, the circle is already formed with you
but the position of this circle is
quite low, so I will
go the circle a little upwards, on the right, that means I have to
take it to this side and the
face of the circle has to be increased a little, okay, on this
side, I have to increase it a little inside the x-axis, so
increase it inside the x axis, so here is
your access, so let's make it
250 here, this
also becomes 250 and take it a little higher
and move it a little here, so let's make
it approximately 270, I am 270 here and let's make it
180 right, I will make it 180
and after that if I run it, see, this
circle becomes 20 and I make its
radius a little and by increasing your radius a little, it will
reduce, so how much should I do, make it
20 here, see,
your hand is also 18 20, so let's
take it a little higher, a
little higher, that means do this  Let's give 160
this is a perfect circle of yours,
inside which his face is completely covered,
so in this way you
can make a circle on this image, now as I
told you that many times we use a circle to hide someone's face,
so how can his face be hidden, I
mean I want to fill it completely
because if I make it then the
thickness will increase a little bit here, if
I also increase the thickness here, then
see, its thickness has increased a lot
here, but this thickness is
increasing towards the outside, yes the thickness that you have
here, that is the boundary of the circle,
as I talk about here, so this is the boundary, what
you are seeing here, this is the
boundary, your thickness is outside this boundary and
not inside, the thickness is increasing, so
you have to fill it
completely, you have to fill it completely, so -1 you
see, you can fill it as I
did here.  So in this way what do you have here,
you can hide any image here, it
means if you want to
hide someone's face here then you
can hide the face by doing this, so
what do you have here, the
circle here reduces,
now let me close it once and
add the thickness back inside it, I will
run the end of 4 here in this way, now you must be
observing one thing inside this, the
circle that we are taking inside this,
inside this circle your face is coming,
some of its hair are also there, so now
this circle here, instead of reducing the circle, it will
reduce the lips because you will see its face, then
how is your face coming, in
this way all your means these original
shapes that you have here are
inside it, this
circle is shape, so at this time it will not
reduce your circle inside the face, so
what will it reduce for you, it will
reduce here, it will reduce the lip, so for now
what did we see, learn to draw a circle here,
now I  Next I will show you
how to make apps here. Let's
learn to make ellipses. So to make lips
I will use this code from here
and show the circle here in
place of this circle. Now the parameters of our ellipse will be
reduced. First I will
see lips here because I have to
make a list. Because I have to make a list, so
I learned lift and inside the ellipse
also there are all the same parameters. Image center
angle color thickness etc. Let's reduce all this for you.
So I will keep it inside here again.
First of all I will talk
about the image.
What is the name of the image? Here is the old image.
So I kept the old image. After that you get
center angle and angle. These are all
important things. So first we will talk about them.
Then color etc. will remain behind. So we will
take them as well. Let's see what are the important things for
us to make lips for any image.
Here first of all I have to
draw this ellipse. What do I have to do? I have to
draw these lips. So to draw ellipse,
first of all you have to do this.  You will have to find the center
from where to draw these lips. The
next thing you have is
its access after the alif. You must have
discussed about lips here earlier in 11th, 12th. So the accesses that
you have are of
two types in this way, in which
you have these
centers. After that, you get the
access access, which means this is your major
access and what is inside it, this is the major
access. So you have to create the major access,
so you have the major access from this
point, which means at what distance is this point from this point.
This point will be ready with you.
Next, this list that you have created,
what is this list?
Actually, the ones that are made, they are
either made on the A axis or are
closed on the X axis. So basically,
these are your accessories. So for this, you
feel that the angle here, this angle will be 30
degrees. The next thing is that you have to
start your lips. Next, you
have to start, which means you have to start from here and  If you have to
come here after doing a complete rotation, then this is your
starting point, if you mean
where to start from and
where to end, you have to give this, so
this angle of 30° is the angle of the lips
and next, the boundary of the
lips that is going on here, from which angle should that boundary
start and from
which angle should it end, you have been given that option,
so you
can give the boundary here from zero to 360° and
hence, you can also
rotate it completely from zero to 360 degrees,
your angle of both is here,
which depends on the angle, let's
see it practically, then you will
understand it more clearly
here, now let me talk
about the center, where to place the center, so the
center of the previous image was the same center, that center was very
correct, so I am
going to copy the same center again, I
want this center only, I don't have to make any change in the center
here now the next thing
So let's create an access here,
inside the access I have to keep it here inside the x-axis
and inside the A axis you have to
come down a little here, so
see inside this it is a little upside down, so
you should take care of that thing a little, so
inside this I will do 50 and
for once, let's see what is going to come in 50 and 100,
here the end angle which
I have to tilt it means at what angle do
I have to trailer, I would
like to settle it at a 30 degree angle, here the
end starting angle as I
told you that I have to make it completely, so I will
give zero and I have to fill the ending angle completely,
so I will have to give 360 ​​here, if we
talk about color, then I have to
give green color, so as you know that
our color is in busy R,
so your B plus has become zero and if we talk about G color, then
my green color is 250 and if we
talk about it, then it has become zero, if we
talk about thickness,
What will you get here, if I take it
above the thickness, then the thickness of
my image should be quite good, I will
take four here and after that, if we
talk about the line type here, then
16 line type is fine, we will learn, so
this is a nice lip, you have it
ready here, but even now
it is not covering up the face completely, so let's
change it a little and
I will make it even better here, so
see, first of all, it will have to be brought a little there, it will have to
come down also, it will have to
look good, so let's change it a little
here,
so the width is correct, I will have to
increase its width here and I will have to increase many other things, so
first of all, let's reduce one thing, that
means your starting angle is
correct, starting is also correct, this is also correct,
color is also correct, thickness is also correct, line type is
also correct, let's change the access a little, let's
change the right exercise a little, so
instead of 50, I will reduce it, I will
make it 100.  If I run it, then it has
become a circle. Okay, because both your axes are
equal, so inside this, I will make an
axe of 70. Yes,
make it around 70, this is enough. 70, and inside this,
increase this as well. Here, it is bigger than 150, right, 150,
so it has become quite big. 150, so let's make
it, it
looks quite correct. And now let's
change its position a little, so
move it a little forward inside the X axis
and move it a little down inside the A axis, let's make
it 300 completely. Let's
complete it once by doing 300, yes, it has become quite big
here, right? It is
300 perfectly. And now this one here,
it has become quite big, right? It is
120. Okay, let's make it 170. So,
now you have it perfect, but
I will have to increase its width a little. So
to increase the width, I will go like this
and make it 80, right?  Your A is done and
because of this 80, now your A has moved a little up and
down here, so let's move it
a little here, yes, try making
it 1860
and increase it here and I will make it 100
here so that it looks a little correct, it got
quite messed up, let's make it 90 here,
95 is
correct, we already have A, now reduce it by one and if we
write the name of our script here,
how good would it be, right? So, let's
put the name inside it so that
it looks a little good, so let's
put the name so that it is good for us to
create the rest of the lips, we have seen here
how your center looks,
how can the access be set, how can the angle be set,
after that your starting
angle, color thickness is online, we have seen this thing
here, now let's write text here,
so
what will I do here, txt underscore here, I will create an image
so that cb2 dot here, what will you
put here, you will have the tax of it here,
right cc tu dot here, for this
I will put C2 dot here  But I will
do that with tax, yes put text,
what will we do, how much tax is there in the tax, so
for tax you will have to
give all these parameters, image phone color
thickness line types etc. and all these
parameters I have to keep with me, so I have
put all these parameters with me,
now first of all let's talk about the image,
what will be the image, so we will have the image, our
old image is our image,
this is our image, next we will talk about the
tax, what will we have with the tax,
what will happen to it now, so I have to take this, let's
talk about the origin, that original
means where do we have to show it here, means
where do we have to show it, basically I go to that
circle which is
rotating here, some part of it should be cut inside the lips
and after cutting some part
I should give tax written nicely there, so
inside it I have to
write somewhere here, let's do a date,
I will comment it out for once,
I will comment out this line
and then after that I will
tell you how you have to do it,
right  And I have commented out this and now if I
run it here, let's do a reduction from
here, I will see here it is
starting, if it is starting from here, it has started
here, you will have an end here,
after the end what do I have to do here, I have to
show my name here,
right here I have to show my name, that
name is going to be shown here, ok and
if I want to fill it, if I
want an image, I want to fill it, then this
thickness is what you should do in place of this thickness,
pass mine van and run it again,
this way your
thickness will be done, your thickness becomes full here,
what is your image, it becomes here, so
you can take it here like this,
now I go back to the same place,
reduce everything like origin etc. back ready, now
I will talk about org,
where do I have to keep the origin, so basically I have to
go forward on this side and also come down on this side, ok so the
center is around 280, so it is around 280, so
increase it a little
What will I do by increasing it here, I will make it
around 400 and if I want to bring the width down then let's make
it 160, this is 160
and after that we will keep adjusting here
and if we talk about font face, then inside the font face
we have many font faces,
you can choose any of them, if we
talk about font scale, then let me do this
after phone face, so I will take phone face
number, I will take face number
here and next now let's talk
about font scale,
what should be the scale of the font, you can take
anything, I will take it in the scale of the font
and after that font color, what kind of font color do you want,
I want red color here, so
for red color, earn zero, earn zero, you have
2:55 this is our phone's end
next now we are talking about the thickness,
how much thickness do we want, so
I will change its thickness here, let's
talk about line then
how much is there for us here 16 and what is the bottom origin  What
we have to do is do a POS for you here,
right because I don't want to show the image in reverse.
Now I will give this tax image, I will
give the date here, in place of our old image,
now what you have, the tax image will
go, so I will pass it inside the tax image, I will
run it, see, it should go
there a little down and go this side,
okay, so it has to come down a little, a
little down, meaning it has to come around 200
and the font scale  If we talk about L, then I want to
show you the scale of one, see this will be true for you,
now here also whose is a little bit, so let's make
it 350 right 350, run
it, what do you understand, now this should be cut, this of
yours should be cut,
it means the starting angle to the ending should go,
here I will reduce this ending angle of
yours, 360 means your proper
rotation, here I will reduce the proper address a
little and make it
around 340, I will run it, so see, this is
how it is visible to you here,
what will be my angle, it has been cut here and the
s has also been increased, now let's increase the thickness of this gift, let's make it, we will
learn from three sizes, so see
how now in this way you
reduce the w one here, green color, see how
cute it will look,
255 and let's make it zero, end it,
how cute it looks, the
thickness is looking a little bad here, try doing it,
exactly how cute it looks
here, this is your space a  Double name is
also added in this way you can show kids here I
think I hope you have understood
how you
can create a PDF on any image and you
can put whatever you want to write like your name etc. on it, right so I think I hope you have
understood so for now
what did we read here today how to
draw a circle and after that how can apps be drawn
Dholak that's all for today's video
see
you with our next video till then stay here with us I
say good bye [
praise]
[music]